let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which collection is ordered, changeable, and allows duplicate members?",
    answer: "LIST ",
    options: [
      "DICTIONARY  ",
      "TUPLE",
      "SET",
      "LIST ",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
    answer: "upper() ",
    options: ["toUpperCase()", "upperCase() ", "upper() ", "uppercase()"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "Which method can be used to replace parts of a string?",
    answer: "replace() ",
    options: [
      "replaceString()",
      "switch()",
      "repl()  ",
      "replace() ",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Which of these collections defines a DICTIONARY?",
    answer: '{"name": "apple", "color": "green"} ',
    options: ['{"name": "apple", "color": "green"} ', '("apple", "banana", "cherry")  ',
     '["apple", "banana", "cherry"]','{"apple", "banana", "cherry"}'],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
    answer: "== ",
    options: ["><", "<>", "== ", "="],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello World' in Python?",
    answer: 'print("Hello World")',
    options: ['echo("Hello World");', 'p("Hello World")', 'print("Hello World")', 'echo "Hello World"'],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How do you insert COMMENTS in Python code?",
    answer: "#This is a comment",
    options: ['#This is a comment', '//This is a comment', '/*This is a comment*/'],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one is NOT a legal variable name?",
    answer: "my-var",
    options: ['my-var', 'Myvar', 'my_var','_myvar'],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
    answer: "Both the other answers are correct ",
    options: ['Both the other answers are correct', 'x = int(5)', 'x = 5'],
  },
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is the correct file extension for Python files?",
  answer: ".py",
  options: ['.py', '.pyth', '.pt','.pyt'],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
    answer: "Both the other answers are correct",
    options: ['Both the other answers are correct', 'x = 2.8', 'x = float(2.8)'],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?",
    answer: "print(type(x))",
    options: ['print(type(x))', 'print(typeOf(x))', 'print(typeof x)', 'print(typeof(x))'],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is the correct way to create a function in Python?",
    answer: "def myFunction():",
    options: ['create myFunction():', 'def myFunction():', 'function myfunction(): '],
  }, 
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which method can be used to remove any whitespace from both the beginning and the end of a string?",
    answer: "strip()  ",
    options: ['len()','strip()  ', 'ptrim() ', 'trim()'],
  },  
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Please, Rate this Portal!",
    answer: "Good",
    options: ["Good", "Need some improvement", "Not good", "None"],
  },
];
